Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Speeches, 1989-2009; 10
  - Veterans, 16
    - National Salute to Hospitalized Veterans, 2004 Feb 13 (Box 187, Folder 69)
    - Departure Ceremony For The 1st Calvary Division, 2004 Feb 16 (Box 187, Folder 70)
    - 49th S.C. O.N.A, 2004 March 6 (Box 187, Folder 71)
    - Waco VA Hospital Announcement, 2004 May 7 (Box 187, Folder 72)
    - U.S. Army War College, 2004 May 12 (Box 187, Folder 73)
    - Vietnam Memorial Dedication — Waco, TX, 2004 May 15 (Box 187, Folder 74)
    - American Legion (HW), 2004 May 24 (Box 187, Folder 75)
    - Protecting a Proven Partnership Service to Veterans, 2005 May 3 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Waco VA Hospital Visit by VA Secretary Nicholson, 2005 July 7 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - 420th Engineering Brigade Return, 2005 Dec 3 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Leadership Meeting (HW), 2006 Feb 8 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - POW/MIA Remembrance, 2006 Sept 17 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Day, 2007 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Houston American Legion Post 490, 2008 Feb 29 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - American Legion (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Army Caucus (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Budget Problems (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Desert Storm: Necessary/How/What Lessons (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Spending as Related to Veterans (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Frost (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Greater Hewitt VFW # 6008, undated (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - Lt. General Tom Metz (Partial), undated (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - MATES (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Day; Hewitt VFW Post 6008 (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - Memorial Day; Killeen/Temple, undated (Box 188, Folder 18)
    - Memorial Day; Temple/4th of July; Rockdale (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 19)
    - Military Appreciation Day; Killeen (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 20)
    - Military Construction and Veterans Affairs Potential Stimulus Items, c. 2009 (Box 188, Folder 21)
    - Military- Ft. Hood, undated (Box 188, Folder 22)
    - Misc. Military Issues (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 23)
    - Notes (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 24)
    - Persian Gulf Remembrance (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 25)
    - Support Our Troops, c. 2002-2003 (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - Task Force Ironhorse, undated (Box 188, Folder 27)
    - “Tribute to the Troops”, undated (Box 188, Folder 28)
    - VA Health Updates/ Tricare (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 29)
    - Veterans and the Cold War (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 30)
    - Veterans Day (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 31)
    - Veterans Forum (HW), 2003 (Box 188, Folder 32)
    - Veteran’s Hospital-Temple, TX (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 33)
    - Veterans Visit Washington, D.C., undated (Box 188, Folder 34)
    - Waco VA Commission (HW), undated (Box 188, Folder 35)
- Voting Record, 1991-2010; 11
  Voting Records include scorecards and data regarding Edwards’ votes compiled by various special interest groups, the Democratic Party, and his own office. These documents are organized chronologically by congress. They include scorecards from organizations such as the Children’s Defense Fund, the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, and the American Civil Liberties Union.
  - General, 1991-2005; 1
    - Agriculture Voting Record, c.1991-2003 (Box 188, Folder 36)
    - Cuts and Savings Revised List, c.1993-1996 (Box 188, Folder 37)
    - Edwards and President Bush, 2005 (Box 188, Folder 38)
    - Letters to Editor, 1993 (Box 188, Folder 39)
  - 101st Congress, 1990; 2
    - CDF Survey, House Voting Record Index, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 40)
  - 102nd Congress, 1991-1992; 3
    - CDF Survey, House Voting Record Index, 1991-1992 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Cuts and Savings, c.1992 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - National Rifle Association Political Preference Chart, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - 103rd Congress, 1991-1995; 4
    - American Federation of Government Employees Scorecard, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee Individual Voting Record, 1991-1994 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Children’s Defense Fund Key House Votes and Voting Record, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Cuts and Savings, c.1994 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Memorandums, 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - National Federation of Independent Business “How Congress Voted” Report, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - 104th Congress, 1993-1997; 5
    - AFL-CIO Final House Voting Record, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Business-Industry Political Action Committee Report Card, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Business-Industry Political Action Committee Voting Record, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Chamber of Commerce “How They Voted”, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Chamber of Commerce Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Children’s Defense Fund “Nonpartisan Congressional Voting Record for 1996”, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Christian Coalition Congressional Scorecards, 1995-1996 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Citizens for a Sound Economy Congressional Voting Record, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Concord Coalition Citizens Council “Tough Choices” Deficit Reduction Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Consumer Federation of America Voting Record, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 19)
    - Cuts and Savings, c.1996 (Box 189, Folder 20)
    - Food Distributors Association Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 21)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Voting Guide, 1st and 2nd Editions, 1995-1996 (Box 189, Folder 22)
    - League of Conservation Voters “100-day Scorecard”, 1995 (Box 189, Folder 23)
    - Memorandums, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 24)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility Children’s Environmental Health Report Card, 1995 (Box 189, Folder 25)
    - Public Citizen Congressional Money and Voting Scorecard, 1995-1996 (Box 189, Folder 26)
    - Responsible Citizens Political League Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 27)
    - UFCW “Major Issues in the House” Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 28)
    - United Church of Christ Voting Record, 1995 (Box 189, Folder 29)
    - U.S. Public Interest Research Group Congressional Scorecard, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 30)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars Endorsement Letter and Voting Record, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 31)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars Scorecard, 1993-1995 (Box 189, Folder 32)
  - 105th Congress, 1995-1998; 6
    - AFL-CIO Final House Voting Record, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 33)
    - AFL-CIO Final House Voting Record, 1998 (Box 189, Folder 34)
    - American Association of University Women, 1995-1997 (Box 189, Folder 35)
    - American Civil Liberties Union “National Freedom” Scorecard, c.1998 (Box 189, Folder 36)
    - The American Conservative Union “Rankings”, 1998 (Box 189, Folder 37)
    - The American Conservative Union “Rating of Congress”, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 38)
    - American Farm Bureau Federation “Friend of Farm Bureau” Award Letter, 1998 (Box 189, Folder 39)
    - American Federation of Government Employees “Voting Record”, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 40)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act Voting Record, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 41)
    - Associated Builders and Contractors, Inc. “How They Voted” Voting Record, c.1997 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Business-Industry Political Action Committee Annual Report Card for Congress, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Campaign for U.N. Reform “The Global Statesmanship Rating Guide”, c.1997 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce “Champion of Free Enterprise” Announcement, c.1997 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Chamber of Commerce “How They Voted”, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Christian Coalition “Congressional Scorecard”, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Christian Coalition Scorecard Memo, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Concord Coalition Citizens Council “Tough Choices” Deficit Reduction Scorecard, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - The Humane Society of the United States Congressional “Scorecard”, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - League of Conservation Voters “1997 National Environmental Scorecard”, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - League of Private Property Voters “Private Property Congressional Vote Index” and Photo, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legislative Report Card, 1997-1998 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - National Farmers Union Award Letter, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - National Federation of Independent Business Congressional Vote Scorecard, c.1998 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - National Journal Annual Congressional Vote Ratings, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - National Journal “Managing the Middle”, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Planned Parenthood Action Fund Congressional Scorecard, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Project Vote Smart “U.S. Government Owner’s [sic] Manual”, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Republicans Education and Labor, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union “Leadership Update”, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 20)
  - 106th Congress, 1999-2000; 7
    - AFL-CIO Final House Voting Record, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - American Civil Liberties Union “National Freedom Scorecard”, 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - American Conservative Union “Legislative Alerts”, c.2000 (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - American Federation of Government Employees Voting Record 106th Congress, 1st Session, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - National Hispanic Leadership Agenda “Congressional Scorecard 106th Congress, 1st Session, 2000 (Box 190, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Chamber of Commerce “Guide to Congress”, 2000 (Box 190, Folder 26)
    - U.S. Chamber of Commerce “How They Voted”, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 27)
  - 107th Congress, 2002; 8
    - National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare Congressional Scorecard, c.2002 (Box 190, Folder 28)
  - 108th Congress, 2004-2005; 9
    - Alliance for Retired Americans Voting Record, 2004 (Box 190, Folder 29)
    - Chamber of Commerce Scorecard, 2005 (Box 190, Folder 30)
    - Farm Bureau Votes, 2004 (Box 190, Folder 31)
  - 111th Congress, 2009-2011; 10
    - Women’s Issues, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 32)
    - Government/Campaign Reform, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 33)
    - Abortion, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 34)
    - Agriculture- Farm Bureau, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 35)
    - Agriculture/Environment/Interior, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 36)
    - Banking, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 37)
    - Defense, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 38)
    - Education, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 39)
    - Energy, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 40)
    - Family Values, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 41)
    - Guns, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 42)
    - Health Care, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 43)
    - Homeland Security, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 44)
    - Housing, Unemployment, and Welfare, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 45)
    - Immigration, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 46)
    - Judiciary, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 47)
    - Labor, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 48)
    - Religious Liberty, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 49)
    - Small Business, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 50)
    - Social Security, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 51)
    - Tax Cuts, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 52)
    - Trade, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 53)
    - Transportation, 2009 -2011 (Box 190, Folder 54)
    - Veterans, 2009-2011 (Box 190, Folder 55)
- Audio-Visual, 1990-2010; 12
  The Audio-Visual Materials of the Chet Edwards collection include images, audio, and video recordings from 1990 to 2010. This material includes television and radio campaign ads, recorded speeches, press reports, and other miscellaneous recordings. The Audio-Visual Materials are divided into seven sections and total 17 linear feet. Material with in each section are organized by data format and includes computer diskettes, video tape reels, audio cassettes, Digital Audio Tapes, VHS tapes, Beta tapes, CDs, and DVDs. Some of the Audio-Visual Material can only be found on the Baylor Digital Collections website in the Poage Legislative Library section. This material is listed under “digital” in the box list.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Beta tapes; Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Digital versatile disk (DVD); Micro video cassettes; Reel to reel tapes; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - Campaigns, 1990-2010, undated; 1
    The campaign series consists of material recorded from 1990 to 2010 (elections from the 102nd to the 111th Congress). The majority of the material includes radio and television spot ads for Chet Edwards by the Democratic media strategist Joe Slade White. Other material includes news recordings on the Edwards’ campaigns, debates, and audio bites for the campaign websites. Also included is material related to Ramsey Farley, Edwards’ opponent in the 2000 and 2002 elections.
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (1 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (2 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (3 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (4 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (5 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (6 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (7 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (8 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (9 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (10 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (11of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (12 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (13 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (14 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (15 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (16 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - 1/4” Audio Tape, “Sweet” (17 of 17), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - Audio Cassette, Chet Edwards with Music, undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Audio Cassette, “McLennan” Radio Spot, 2000 Oct 25 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Audio Cassette, “Claim” Radio Spot, 2000 Oct 27 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Audio Cassette, “Meals” Radio Spot, 2000 Oct 30 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Audio Cassette, “Claim” Radio Spot, 2000 Oct 31 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Audio Cassette, Untitled, undated (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - DAT - Digital Audio Tape, Audio Bites for Web Site: 2 Versions, 2002 April 18 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - VHS, Murphy Putnam Media, Inc., Demonstration Reel, 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - VHS, Struble Oppel Eichenbaum, Demo Reel, 2002 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - VHS, “Edwards TV Campaigns ’92 ’94 ’96”, 1992, 1994, 1996 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - VHS, “Schools” TV, 2000 Aug 30 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - VHS, “Education” TV, 2000 Aug 31 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - VHS, “Promise” TV, 2000 Sept 7 (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - VHS, “Protect” TV, 2000 Sept 18 (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - VHS, “Soldiers” TV, 2000 Sept 26 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - VHS, “Classroom”, 2000 Oct 4 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - VHS, “Clifton” TV, 2000 Oct 13 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - VHS, “Clifton” TV, 2000 Oct 16 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - VHS, “Failed” TV, 2000 Oct 19 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - VHS, “Wheels” TV, 2000 Oct 26 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - VHS, “Meals” TV, 2000 Oct 26 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - VHS, “Harriman” TV, 2000 Nov 2 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - VHS, “Higher” and “Anything” TV, 2000 Nov 3 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - VHS, 2000 Demo Reel with Log, Joe Slade White & Co., Inc., 2001 April 6 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - VHS, Production Cost Reel, Joe Slade White & Co., Inc., 2001 May 18 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - VHS, “Best of 2000” Reel with Log, Joe Slade White & Co., Inc., 2001 Aug 8 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - VHS, “Mystery” TV, 2002 July 18 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - VHS, “Chet Edwards for Congress” Tape #1, Camera Rolls 1-5, 2002 Sept 4 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - VHS, “Chet Edwards for Congress” Tape #2, Camera Rolls 6-8, 2002 Sept 4 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - VHS, “Responsibility” TV, 2002 Sept 10 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - VHS, CBS The Early Show, “Decision” Ad & Ramsey Farley Ad, 2000 Oct 11 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - VHS, Edwards & Farley Open House Campaign Ads on Local TV, 2000 Aug 26 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - VHS, Farley Campaign Finances, KCEN NBC 6, 2002 July 12 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - VHS, KXXV ABC 25 6pm News: Farley, 10pm News, & KCEN NBC 6, 2002 July 15 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - VHS, Chet Edwards Political Commercials, KCEN NBC 6:30am News, 2002 July 24 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - VHS, Farm Bureau, KCEN NBC 6 6pm & 10pm News, 2002 Aug 8 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - VHS, Farm Bureau, KXXV ABC 25 6pm News, 2002 Aug 8 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - VHS, Debate/Hastert, KCEN NBC 6 10pm News, 2002 Sept 28 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - VHS, KWTX CBS 10 6pm & 10pm News, 2002 Sept 28 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - VHS, KXXV ABC 25 5pm, 6pm, & 10pm News, 2002 Oct 14 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - VHS, KWTX CBS 10 6pm & 10pm News (Nov 1); Chet Edwards and Ramsey Farley Forum (Nov 2), 2002 Nov 1-2 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - VHS, KWTX CBS 10 News, 2002 Nov 4 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - VHS, KXXV ABC 25 News, 2002 Nov 4 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley, “Standing With,” Impeachment & Chet, 2000 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley, “Popular With,” Hillary & Chet, 2000 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley, “Seniors”, 2000 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley TV Ads, TX-11 Primary/Runoff 2000 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - VHS, Edwards/Farley Forum, 2000 Oct 9 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley Interview, KCEN NBC 6, 2000 Oct 23 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - VHS, Ramsey Farley “Marriage” ad, 2000 Oct 28 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - VHS, Killeen Exchange Club, Ramsey Farley & Chet Edwards, 2002 Sept 23 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - VHS, Edwards/Farley Debate, KCEN NBC 6, 2002 Sept 28 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - VHS, Kay Bailey Hutchinson; Ramsey Farley Ad, undated (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - VHS, “Marvin,” Spot Ad for Chet Edwards by Marvin Leath, 1990 Nov 2 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - VHS, “Edwards - Common Sense,” Texas Democratic Party, 2002 Sept 10 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - VHS C, VHS Adapter, undated (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - VHS C, AARP, Veterans Issues, Chet Edwards and Ramsey Farley, 2000 Oct 9 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - VHS C, AARP, Chet Edwards, 2000 Oct 9 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - VHS C, AARP, Ramsey Farley, 2000 Oct 9 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - VHS C, AARP Q&A, Closing, undated (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - VHS C, Chet Edwards - Ramsey Farley Killeen Exchange Club, 2002 Sept 23 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - 1” Type C, “Balance,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 3), 1996 Aug 28 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - 1” Type C, “Balance,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 3), 1996 Aug 28 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - 1” Type C, “Balance,” Chet Edwards for Congress (3 of 3), 1996 Aug 28 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - 1” Type C, “Power,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 2), 1996 Aug 30 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - 1” Type C, “Power,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 2), 1996 Aug 30 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - 1” Type C, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 5), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - 1” Type C, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 5), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - 1” Type C, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (3 of 5), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - 1” Type C, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (4 of 5), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - 1” Type C, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (5 of 5), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - 1” Type C, “Fare,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 2), 1996 Sept 9 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - 1” Type C, “Fare,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 2), 1996 Sept 9 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - 1” Type C, “Check,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 4), 1996 Sept 30 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - 1” Type C, “Check,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 4), 1996 Sept 30 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - 1” Type C, “Check,” Chet Edwards for Congress (3 of 4), 1996 Sept 30 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - 1” Type C, “Check,” Chet Edwards for Congress (4 of 4), 1996 Sept 30 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - 1” Type C, “Low,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 4), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - 1” Type C, “Low,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 4), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - 1” Type C, “Low,” Chet Edwards for Congress (3 of 4), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - 1” Type C, “Low,” Chet Edwards for Congress (4 of 4), 1996 Oct 29 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - 1” Type C, “Higher” & “Anything,” Chet Edwards for Congress, 2000 Nov 3 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - BetacamSP, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (1 of 3), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - BetacamSP, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (2 of 3), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - BetacamSP, “Opportunity,” Chet Edwards for Congress (3 of 3), 1996 Sept 5 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - BetacamSP, “Higher” & “Anything,” Chet Edwards for Congress, 2000 Nov 3 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - 3/4” Umatic, “Higher” & “Anything,” Chet Edwards for Congress, 2000 Nov 3 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - CD, “Communities Together,” Radio PSA, 2002 Feb 21 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - CD, Audio bites for Web site: 2 versions, 2002 April 18 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - DVD, Chet Edwards for Congress 2008, 2008 Nov 7 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - DVD, Chet Edwards for Congress 2010, 2010 Nov 9 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - DVD, Chet Edwards for Congress 2010, 2010 Dec 15 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Events, 1995-2010, undated; 2
    The Events subseries consists of images and videos of various events Edwards attended during his time in office. The dates of this section range from 1995 to 2010 and include charity events, Congressional Delegation visits to military bases, ceremonies, forums, and conferences. Events related specifically to the military can be found in the Topical subseries (VI) under “military.”
    - VHS, United Methodist Men Washington Conference, undated (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - VHS, Info-Net Dedication Ceremony, Central Texas Telephone Co-op, 1995 March 2 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - VHS, Financial Aid Forum, Chet Edwards, Central Texas College, 1995 April 12 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - CD, Ted C. Connell Terminal Groundbreaking, 2003 March 21 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - CD, 9000 Toy Donation, Santa’s Workshop, 2004 Nov 13 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - CD, Brazos Family Medicine Mobile Medical Unit “Hippocrates,” Photos, 2005 July 8-2005 Sept 14, 2005 Sept 28 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - CD, VA Reception for Chet Edwards, 2007 Aug 22 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - CD, Bryan, TX Grand Opening, Photos (1 of 2), 2007 Sept 19 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - CD, Bryan, TX Grand Opening, Photos (2 of 2), 2007 Sept 19 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - CD, CODEL Visit to Ft. Riley & Ft. Leavenworth, Photos, 2008 Jan (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - CD, Texas A&M Signing, Congressman Edwards, 2009 April 30 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - CD, National Guard Association of the United States (NGAUS) 132nd Conference, Austin, TX, Rep. Edwards, Pictures, 2010 Aug 22 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - DVD, T.B. Maston Speech, Chet Edwards, 2005 Nov 17 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - DVD, President Bush and Chet Edwards, Veteran’s Day, American Legion Post 121, KTWX CBS 10, 2007 Nov 11 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - DVD, Texas A&M Conference 2008, 2008 March 13 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - DVD, Texas A&M AgriLIFE Conference 2008 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - DVD, National Guard Association of the United States (NGAUS) 132nd Conference, Austin, TX, Rep. Edwards, Video, 2010 Aug 22 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Local and National Coverage, 1991-2009, undated; 3